Shubhendu did the construction at the time I don't know who is
this system is right or well
organized, through Beawar City Ministry, on the
topic of Pichola, everyone said their own thing, did
not tell anyone that you should speak,
such doctors turned them next to Gulhad,
remind them that the office was
very nice,
quid if it also goes to your members
who introduced us,
what is digitization, now you are
asked by subscribing, you had demonetization,
that was the topic and have been appointed for a great interview,
in mehndi and file, I mean tell me, there should
not be any evil eye there, you will be confident
because there I told me
that I am in
9th now, then whatever is coming, tell me the
video, let me tell you, there was an
interview in Sainik School and his mother and
children and in subscription, Sanskrit,
English, otherwise they helped a lot,
Patan,
what are you saying, is there
any one point, yes,
some people of Haryana should play, all the people have come, Priya Rani is
also coming,
phone number three song video comedy last
loot
first  Tell us your experience, how many times did
you say what happened in GD, what did they say, give us your
experience, this is before that you used to do
first step celebs,
subscribe to
loot for a minute, whatever they said, it used to
battery you, it is not my habit, I used to
talk to you guys like this, I mean a little bit, on the
mirror, there she hangs
against you, do not forget to subscribe to these people, the
police is sitting in it, Ronit, Ronit
Roy, that is,
Dimple, I said and there was a girl,
she said twice, I will not say anything to
them, do not forget to subscribe
and subscribe to my channel,
click on your interview and subscribe, 63,
this Siddhant will, after hardly 1 minute, I
showed it to the farmers, I mean the writers,
wrote on my Twitter page and
went to her and asked, tell me in the interview, tell me your
qualification, Sumiratna Mahal, quarter inch
and I want to go to Amazon shopping,
in the reality period, there was a fog, I was very
happy ma'am, that is why I gave the interview,
when I was still different, interview, my
urad and introduction in this field, I
clicked on subscribe, subscribe  You
could not subscribe after the first
interview, I mean, the one who
went to ICICI, I said
no sir, then another question, what did you do,
he said all the best for a minute, is it
not that you people ask questions, whoever has to give the
interview, Sanskriti, you must ask questions,
dear,
you should also ask questions if you want to give an interview, yes, absolutely,
if you try to give an interview, then
you should ask questions, they are the
most beneficial, you should
ask things of your level, what will happen if this happens, anybody can
you, very special
to Ajay